fitnessconnectionusa.com 2013-09-25

# Fitness Connection, Texas, Nevada And North Carolina

## **FitnessConnectionUSA.com Privacy Policy  
This Privacy Policy is effective on February 10, 2012.**

## General

This Privacy Policy describes the practices that Titan Fitness, LLC, doing business as Fitness Connection (referred to herein as "Titan Fitness" or "we") follows with respect to the collection and use of information submitted on fitnessconnectionusa.com (the "Site"). This Privacy Policy applies only to information we collect from this Site, and does not apply to any other website or business activity of Titan Fitness. By using our Site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by us.

We reserve the right to revise this policy at any time. When we do, we will give you notice of the revised Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site and by revising the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those changes. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the current privacy policy.

## Information We Collect

We collect "personally identifiable information" and "automatic information."

"Personally identifiable information" is information that tells us who you are, such as your name, email address, street address, telephone number, payment information, and other personal attributes and characteristics. We may collect personally identifiable information when you purchase a membership, request a pass to visit our facilities or if you otherwise voluntarily choose to provide it to us. In the event that we permit users to create online accounts, we may also collect personally identifiable information during the registration process.

You can choose not to provide personally identifiable information to us. However, if you do not provide such information, you may be unable to use or access certain portions of the Site. For example, you may be unable to purchase a membership online, request a free pass to visit our facilities or, if offered, create an online account.

"Automatic information" is information automatically collected by our Web server (which may be hosted by a third-party) that your web browser makes available whenever you visit our Site, such as your computer's browser type, IP address, operating system version, and your type of mobile device, geographic location and browsing activity.

We may also use cookies or other commonly used techniques for understanding your preferences and interests, and we may direct content or advertising to you based on those preferences or interests.

A cookie is a text file that a website's server places on a computer's Web browser. The cookie may be used to transmit information back to the website's server about the browsing activities of the computer user on the site (e.g., pages and content viewed, the time and duration of visits, search queries entered into search engines, and whether a computer user clicked on an advertisement). We may also use cookies to track a computer user across different sites in order to provide advertisements to them. If you would prefer not to accept cookies from our Site or any other site, you may be able to modify the setting on your specific Web browser. However, if you refuse to accept cookies, it is possible that some portions of the Site may not function as intended.

## Disclosure and Use of Information We Collect

We use personally identifiable information for the purpose(s) for which it is provided and for the other purposes specified herein. For example, we may use personally identifiable information to send you a free pass to visit our facilities, to process your purchase of a membership and, if offered, to create your online account. We may also use your personally identifiable information to communicate with you for marketing, educational and promotional purposes, to respond to emails, and to provide customer support.

We may provide your personally identifiable information to third parties who provide services to us and/or on our behalf. These third parties may provide a variety of services to us including, without limitation, hosting this Site, providing technical support, processing and storing user information, updating your customer information records in our database, and sending or coordinating the sending of marketing communications on our behalf. We may disclose personally identifiable information to affiliated companies, our parent company and sister companies.

We may use automatic information to help us run, maintain and improve our Site, customize the visitor's experience, study traffic patterns, and generally learn about the usage of the Site.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who may have breached any terms and conditions posted on our Site, or who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other users of our Site, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may also disclose personally identifiable information when we reasonably believe that the law requires it.

We might sell or buy subsidiaries or business units. In such transactions, personally identifiable information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy. Also, in the unlikely event that our assets are sold, personally identifiable information may be one of the transferred assets.

## Privacy of Children

The Site is a general audience website. We do not intentionally collect personally identifiable information from users of this Site who are under the age of thirteen.

If we become aware that a user of our Site is under the age of 13 and has placed an order using our Site, we will remove that child's personal information from our files.

## Updating Your Information

If you would like to review and/or request changes to any of your personally identifiable information provided to us through the Site, you may do so by contacting us at [customerservice@fitnessemail.net](mailto:customerservice@fitnessemail.net). If you no longer wish to receive communications from us, or otherwise wish to change your communication preferences, you may do so by following the instructions and/or links in the emails sent by us or on our behalf.

## Security

Information transmitted on the Internet and/or stored on systems attached to the Internet is not 100 percent secure. As a result, we do not ensure, warrant or guarantee the security or integrity of such information. We will not be responsible for disclosure of any information due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.

## Links to Other Websites

While you are using this Site, you may be linked or directed to other third party sites outside of the Site that are beyond our control. Each of these third party sites may have a privacy policy different from ours. For example, you might click on a link or banner ad that will take you off the Site. These links and banners may take you to sites of advertisers, sponsors and co-branding partners. Please review the privacy policies of these sites. We are not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

## Contact Information

Please send any concerns regarding our privacy policy to [customerservice@fitnessemail.net](mailto:customerservice@fitnessemail.net).
